Motocrossed! is a tv movie, family, comedy film directed by Steve Boyum.
Teenage Andrea Carson who loves motocross, despite her father finding her
unsuited for the sport, being that she is "just a girl".
When her twin brother Andrew breaks his leg just before a big race, their
father is forced to go to Europe to find a replacement rider.
In the meantime, Andrea secretly races in Andrew's place with her mother's help.
Andrea 'Andi' Carson, played by Alana Austin.
Dean Talon, played by Riley Smith.
Edward Carson, played by Timothy Carhart.
Andrew Carson, played by Trever O'Brien.
Jason Carson, played by Scott Terra.
Bob Arness, played by Mark Curry.
Motocrossed is a 2001 American sports drama film released as a Disney Channel Original Movie about a girl named Andrea Carson who
loves motocross, despite the fact that her father finds her unsuited for the sport, being that she is "just a girl".
When her twin brother Andrew dislocates his knee just before a big race, their
father is forced to go to Europe to find a replacement rider.
In the meantime, Andrea secretly races in Andrew's place with her mother's help.
The movie is a loose adaptation of William Shakespeare's Twelfth Night.
The film also had a lot of product placement with many of the clothing, motocross gear and bikes seen
from real extreme sports companies including Vans, Suzuki, No Fear and Fox Racing.
The film explores themes of sports, motocross, cross dressing,
shakespeare in modern dress, gender disguise.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.